<Project-div name="Mapdiver">
	<Folder-div name="Functional Requirements">
		<Requirement-div id="R1" name="Map-Display">
			The application must display a map on the main webpage after a loading time. There should also be a top sticky header.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R2" name="Map-Interaction">
			Users must be able to interact with four types of elements on the map:
				station_label
				station
				ligne_label
				ligne_tracks
			Clicking on any of these elements should change the corresponding colors on the webpage.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R3" name="Search-Functionality">
			A search bar must be present in a sticky header at the top of the page.
			Users must be able to search for station_label or ligne_label by name.
			The search results should highlight the relevant element on the map.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R4" name="Left-Panel-Hamburger-Menu">
			The application must have a hamburger menu on the sticky that opens a left panel when clicked.
			The left panel must contain text indications (instructions or information).
			The left panel must include a switch list, where each switch can change the color of an element on the main map.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R20" name="loading-specific-page">
			When loading a specific line or station the application should directly load on the station.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Folder-div name="Right-panel">
			<Requirement-div id="R23" name="right-panel-opening">
				When clicking on a station the right panel should be displayed and show information about the selected object.
				Clickig on the cross inside should reset the map.
			</Requirement-div>
			<Requirement-div id="R25" name="display information about a line">
				When clicking on a line it should correctly display information about the map, it's name with the icon. and the schedule associated to the line.
			</Requirement-div>
			<Requirement-div id="R26" name="display information about a Station">
				When clicking on Station it should display the name of the station and all the relation at that station. it should segment all schedule into directions 
			</Requirement-div>
		</Folder-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R24" name="resizing the GUI">
			The user can resize the screen and the map should adapts its size
		</Requirement-div>
	</Folder-div>

	<Folder-div name="UI/UX Requirements">
		<Requirement-div id="R5" name="Sticky-Header">
			The sticky header must always remain visible when scrolling or grabbing the screen.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R6" name="Hamburger-Menu-Accessibility">
			The hamburger menu must be accessible and easy to use. changing its state as the user click on it
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R7" name="Map-Interactions">
			The map interactions should be smooth with visual feedback when elements are selected. the user should be able to scrool and smooth up to it's defined limits
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R8" name="Search-Results-Display">
			The search results should be clearly displayed.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R9" name="Left-Panel-Styling">
			The left panel should be properly styled and not obstruct key functionalities.
		</Requirement-div>
	</Folder-div>

	<Folder-div name="Performance Requirements">
		<Requirement-div id="R10" name="Map-Loading-Speed">
			The map must load within 3 seconds on a stable internet connection and begin the zoom animation when loaded.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R11" name="Interaction-Response-Time">
			Interactions (clicking on elements, toggling switches) should have a response time of less than 5ms including easing animation time.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R12" name="Search-Performance">
			The search functionality should return results almost instantly.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R13" name="Panel-Open-Close-Speed">
			The left panel must open and close smoothly within 3ms including easing animation time.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R22" name="map-navigation">
			The user can navigate on the map
		</Requirement-div>
	</Folder-div>

	<Folder-div name="Accessibility Requirements">
		<Requirement-div id="R14" name="Keyboard-Navigation">
			the search bar should be navigable with the keyboard
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R16" name="Screen-Reader-Compatibility">
			The application should be compatible with most scale readers on desktop.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R21" name="Easy color mode">
			The User can change the color mode displayed on the map.
		</Requirement-div>
		<Requirement-div id="R27" name="State Poping">
			The user can navigate using back and forward button
		</Requirement-div>
	</Folder-div>

	<Folder-div name="Security-And-Data-Handling-Requirements">
	</Folder-div>
</Project-div>